no I am not going to stop trading a
couple of days ago I posted on my
Instagram that I was thinking about
stopping trading because I have pretty
much achieved everything that I wanted
from it it became very boring very
systematical and I just thought I was
done with it and I wanted to focus on
something else different type of markets
but then I realized that I can't stop
trading because there's this one thing I
haven't achieved and this one thing has
been haunting me ever since I haven't
completed it for the last 8 n months
literally thinking about it every single
day how I let myself down and you guys
and that is the 100 to the mail
challenge in August 6th of
2023 I started my first attempt to
turning a $100 into a million dollar
little did I know what challenges this
had ahead of me and this was the
challenge the series The Daily battles
that literally turned me into the trader
that I am today I learned so much over
the course of these 3 to four months
where I successfully flipped $100 all
the way to
$360,000 but it got to the point where I
started hating trading I didn't love the
journey I didn't feel the same about it
because I was almost just forcing it it
got to the point where I just wanted to
get the challenge out of the way and I
was getting tired of trading London
session New York session every single
day because I had a very hard schedule
and I had so much stuff going around at
the time I had just moved into a new
house there were so many things
attacking at the same time that I wasn't
really doing the challenge Cheng for
myself I was just doing it because I
decided to start something that nobody
has ever done and as I started it I
didn't realize the battles that I was
going to face and I didn't realize how
much pressure I was going to be under
and I'm not the kind of person to ever
quit on anything and I wasn't just going
to stop halfway through it and I
actually never opened up and said this
before but I wanted to stop the
challenge as soon as I got to 100K the
fact that I turned $100 to $100,000 was
absolutely insane to me but I saw the
love and the feedback that you guys gave
to me and I said you know what I can't
stop here I had to keep going and that's
where more stress came in and it just
started turning more into a hate
relationship versus love relationship
that I would have with the markets and
all of these battles and all of these
things that I faced is something that
now I am ready for it because I have
already experienced it I learned from it
and now when I'm going to begin this new
100 to the mill challenge I know exactly
what I'm going to be facing and for
those of you guys that have no idea what
I'm talking about about a year ago I
tried to take $100 to a million dollar
and I documented every single trade
before I took it as soon as I took it
and after I took it I shared every
single trade on my Instagram telegram
live streams I was literally showing you
guys how all you need is the proper
skill set in order to succeed in trading
you don't need a large amount of capital
in order to actually make money from
Trading once you learn the skill set the
money that you can make from Trading is
literally as much as you want and one of
the main things that I learned in this
journey of my first attempt to the 100
to the mail because keep in mind never
previously in my life have I ever done a
successful flip now I've maybe turned
10,000 to 30 40,000 or a couple thousand
to maybe 10,000 but never something so
exponential I taken something as small
as $100 to then six figures so this is
my actual first attempt to doing it and
I got so much awareness and so much love
from all of you guys the series alone
got millions of views that I said I
can't let the people down I have I have
to keep this going but as I kept it
going I got to the point where it pretty
much broke me that I even had to leave
social media and take a little of a
break because the pressure was insane
and you know looking back at all that
stuff that I went to I realized that I
just wasn't ready for it and the fact
that I actually made it to that far was
pretty much impressive because it was my
first time actually doing it now fast
forward a year later I am a completely
different person I'm older more
experienced and now I am 100% ready to
take on this 100 to the m and all the
mistakes that I made I haven't written
down and I learned from them one of the
main ones is going to be look out for
the news when I actually trade I never
look for news and when trading the
account on the last days of it before I
actually blew it it's because I got
caught in between an NFP news which are
the main news that happen at the
beginning of the first Friday of every
month now I have that calendarized and I
know exactly what to look out for and
those days that I'm going to be trading
I'm going to make sure to either
minimize my risk or simply not trade
second is going to be to not travel and
trade so I've traveled literally all
around the world right before I'm
starting this challenge so I can
literally lock in dial in and only focus
on the challenge because I was actually
trading outside of my home office
because they were doing renovations in
my house and I couldn't focus because
they were pretty much breaking down a
bathroom and one of the closets so I had
to go and stay at an apartment building
in the city and I just was out of my
comfort zone and you add news on top of
that it was just pretty much an equation
for failure so those are two main things
that I learned from that challenge and
then the Third is I don't have to put so
much pressure on myself on having those
hard targets every single week my goals
was to double up the account every
single week no matter what and I was
taking trades that I shouldn't have and
luckily it all played in my favor
because I was in a very good winning
streak throughout the market but I
didn't have to put that amount of
pressure on myself because I was staying
up during London session when I didn't
have to and I was staying up New York
session when I didn't sleep London
session that would have just affected my
regular day-to-day life and my work life
balance come now this new challenge I'm
going to do this correctly I'm going to
do this so any single person out there
can handedly copy every single step that
I'm going to do with this 100 to the
mill challenge even if you have a job
even if you have all the free time in
the world I'm going to make this as
simple and as effective as possible so
everybody can replicate it better than
what I did last time this time I'm
bigger stronger and better than ever and
if you guys haven't seen the series
turning $100 into a million is really
not that difficult you just have to
pretty much double your accounts every
single week or every single two weeks
and with compound interest and a
positive risk reward of a minimum of a 1
to2 one to three risk reward you can
successfully flip the account all the
way up to a million or even past a
million the only highrisk thing is that
you're obviously risking a lot of the
account I was risking 50 to
75% of the account every single time I
would to take a trade now this is not
sustain aable type of trading but you
start off with 100 bucks once you're at
20,000 and say you risk half of that
it's not a big deal it's not your money
technically it's profits from the market
so I wasn't attached to the money I was
more attached to the stress and the
journey that I was kind of putting you
guys to it because what I would record I
would document it and show it you guys
and I don't want to transmit stress
because trading shouldn't be that way
trading should be something that is done
seamlessly when you follow a trading
plan and a system and just to add a
little bit more and go a little bit
deeper into the subject the art of
flipping an account is simply taking the
highest probability trade you don't want
to take a bunch of little trades in
order to flip an account that's not the
goal you don't want to take a bunch of
different trades and see which one hits
and see which ones don't you simply want
to wait when you have a really really
really really really good trade setup
and you pretty much just risk everything
on that trade now if you wait 5 6 7 8 n
days for one trade to appear and
everything checks out on it the odds of
it winning are higher than not so why
would you not bet 5050 to 60% of the
account obviously if you're with a flip
account mindset I don't do this with my
personal account I don't do this with
any other ones of my accounts I only do
this when I'm flipping it and I've
actually been you know flipping a little
bit of the accounts over the course of
the last two three months just to see if
I still have it and I definitely still
have it I've successfully flipped many
different accounts and it leads me to
this point to just confirm that all you
need for a successful flip is going to
be to wait for a really really good
trade setup that would consist of
multiple time frames in sync a strong
level of area of interest and a very
very strategic and positive entry signal
is going to be key to when you go risk
50 to 60% of your account on this trade
the odds of you winning are a lot higher
versus losing whenever you execute this
trade you want to make sure you have a
minimum of a three risk to reward 1 to
two 1 to three so that 50% of the
account that you risk now you are up
technically 150% 200% of the account
obviously when you're talking 100 bucks
two3 $400 it's really not much when you
take that same percentage to then 10,000
so then 50,000 then 100,000 then you
start growing really really really fast
and the Arts of flipping is not being
attached to the money because if you can
flip an account from 100 to 200 that's
just one flip there's no difference in
percentage wise taking 10,000 to 20,000
20,000 to 40,000 40 to 80 it's all the
same percentage don't even that changes
is the numbers on the screen and you
have to be very experienced and very
nonchalant and stoic to not let that
affect you and that is what I was not
prepared previously in The Challenge
from com out to this challenge I give a
about the money all I care about is
achieving this and showing you guys that
it is possible for you guys to do it so
now coming into this new 100 to thee
Mill challenge part two there is nothing
that I'm going to change in my strategy
my strategy is exactly the same my risk
is going to be exactly the same the type
of markets that I trade are going to be
exactly the same there's only couple
things that are going to change and
there's a couple of rules that I'm going
to be implementing which are going to be
the following the first is every single
trade that I'm going to take just as
before I have to share across my whole
entire social media so all of you guys
can follow along and see the trade for
yourselves the second is going to be
that I can only trade in the Foreign
Exchange Market I cannot trade cryptos
which are going crazy right now and I
can't trade any stocks or options I have
to stick to my foreign exchange markets
and nothing outside of that and then
third is that I cannot take any signals
anybody else's bias anybody it's just my
trade analysis and nobody else's
previously I was looking at some of my
students analysis and it kind of
affected a little bit me even though I
didn't pay attention to it just
subconsciously got in my mind but now in
this challenge I'm only going to focus
on my trades and nobody else's trades
and just to assure of that I am going to
be personally sending the trades out in
my Instagram in my Telegram in my
Discord so you guys can have the exact
same Journey as me it's going to be
crazy because this is as transparent as
it gets and nobody has ever done this
before and honestly I'm more confident
than ever that I could achieve this
simply because I'm starting right around
the same time that I did last year
meaning that the market should have that
winning streak that I had come last year
and on top of that I I'm just ready I
can almost feel it I can see the markets
lining up I've practiced it in the last
two three months with a little bit
bigger accounts and I've successfully
done it and I've actually looked back
through the whole entire series of me
turning the $100 to the mill and I would
literally see days that I would be
emotional days that I wouldn't be
emotional I would spot the mistakes in
myself my trading was absolutely
impeccable the trades were perfect the
risk management was perfect takeprofit
stop loss everything was perfect but the
Trader that was executing that strategy
at that time wasn't the trader that was
meant for that success I believe the
trader that I am now I am two three even
four times bigger than who I was just a
year ago in terms of mindset and
experience that now I'm more confident
than ever that I could achieve this and
the accounts that I have been previously
flipping has been with the markets that
I have analyzed with my students every
single week that I do on Sunday swings
and literally two weeks ago I did a free
Sunday swings for the first time here in
my YouTube channel and we got over a
100,000 people that tuned in to the
stream where we had a beautiful
beautiful Market line up on Sunday and
it ended up playing out by Wednesday
that was a trade that I actually made
$200,000 on and all the hundreds of
thousands of traders that got on the
stream they actually saw it live so I'm
going to be doing maybe a free SUNY
swings every month or every month and a
half the only way for you to find out is
if you hit that subscribe button and
turn on the notification Bell because
not only are you going to be part of
this Legend legendary series of
attempting to turn $100 into a million
once again but you're going to be part
of a free live stream that I'm going to
be sharing with you the markets before
they happen a week in advance so if for
whatever reason you can capitalize off
of it with the telegram or the Instagram
you're literally going to be part of the
Sunday before it actually happens so hit
the Subscribe buttton make sure you turn
on the notification Bell and I will see
you guys in the series